<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_failure_init">Failed to initialize ViviTrento application</string>
    <string name="overflow">More</string>

    <!-- Edit Fragment -->
    <string name="modify">Modifica</string>
    <string name="start_url">http://</string>
    <string name="city_hint">Rovereto</string>
    <string name="day_hint">giorno</string>
    <string name="time_hint">ora</string>
    <string name="event_desc_hint">descrivi qui l\'evento</string>
    <string name="info_txt">Informazione</string>
    <string name="what_txt">Descrizione</string>
    <string name="title_txt">Titolo</string>
    <string name="origin_txt">Promotore</string>
    <string name="contacts_txt">Contatti</string>
    <string name="event_no_information">No information available</string>
    <string name="invalid_emails">Email non valide: \'%1$s\'</string>
    <string name="invalid_phones">Numeri di telefono non validi: \'%1$s\'</string>
    <string name="invalid_email">Email non valida</string>
    <string name="invalid_phone">Numero di telefono non valido</string>
    <string name="invalid_weburl">web url non valida</string>
    <string name="invalid_fburl">facebook url non valida</string>
    <string name="invalid_twitterurl">twitter url non valida</string>
    <string name="tag_remove_request">Vuoi eliminare il tag \'%1$s\'?</string>
    <string name="info_remove_request">Vuoi eliminare l\'info \'%1$s\'?</string>
    <string name="phone_remove_request">Vuoi eliminare il telefono \'%1$s\'?</string>
    <string name="email_remove_request">Vuoi eliminare l\'email \'%1$s\'?</string>
    <string name="fieldtype_remove_alert">\'%1$s\' non contiene informazioni e verrà eliminato. Vuoi aggiungere informazioni?</string>
    <string name="missing_fieldtype_values_alert">\'%1$s\' non contiene informazioni e non verrà aggiunto. Vuoi aggiungere informazioni?</string>
    <string name="missing_fieldtype_alert">Non hai specificato il tipo di info da aggiungere. Vuoi farlo ora?</string>
    <string name="yes">Si</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="new_field_type_label">Che tipo di info vuoi aggiungere?</string>
    <string name="addnewinfo">Aggiungi nuove informazioni</string>
    <string name="insert_info">Inserisci informazioni</string>

    <!-- MainActivity -->
    <string name="nav_drawer_map">Eventi</string>
    <string name="empty" />
    <string name="categories_event_cultura">Cultura</string>
    <string name="categories_event_sport">Sport</string>
    <string name="categories_event_social">Social</string>
    <string name="categories_event_altri_eventi">Altri eventi</string>

    <!-- Create/Update Operations -->

    <string name="event_create_success">Evento screato con successo!</string>
    <string name="categories_info_news">Notizie</string>
    <string name="categories_info_organizations">Distretti e organizzazioni</string>
    <string name="categories_track_pedestrian">Piste ciclopedonali</string>
    <string name="categories_track_trekking">Passeggiate</string>
    <string name="categories_track_bicycle">Pista ciclabile</string>
    <string name="source_smartcampus">SmartCampus</string>
    <string name="backstring">Indietro</string>
    <string name="showdetails">Dettagli&#8230;</string>
    <string name="info_dialog_title_poi">Informazioni luogo</string>
    <string name="info_dialog_title_event">Informazioni evento</string>
    <string name="info_dialog_title_track">Informazioni tracciato</string>
    <string name="app_failure_obj_not_found">Oggetto non trovato!</string>

    <!-- Event Info Contacts -->
    <string name="event_category">Evento %1$s, promosso da %2$s</string>
    <string name="categories_event_today">Eventi di oggi</string>
    <string name="categories_event_my">I miei eventi</string>
    <string name="search_txt">Cerca</string>
    <string name="comments">Vedi recensioni</string>
    <string name="event_no_comments">Non ci sono commenti</string>
    <string name="submenu_related_events">Eventi in programma</string>
    <string name="search_in_category">nella categoria</string>
    <string name="search_today_events">Eventi di oggi</string>
    <string name="eventlist_at_place">Eventi a</string>
    <string name="toast_poi_not_found">Luogo non trovato</string>
    <string name="warning_for_direction">Attenzione! Le indicazioni stradali ti porteranno nella sede dell\'organizzatore e non nella sede dell\'evento.</string>
    <string name="list_event_today">Oggi</string>
    <string name="list_event_tomorrow">Domani</string>
    <string name="content_empty">Nessun risultato.</string>
    <string name="app_failure_security">Recupero delle informazioni di autenticazione non riuscito!</string>
    <string name="app_failure_operation">OOPS! C\'è stato un errore. Controlla la connessione e riprova a breve.</string>
    <string name="initial_data_load">Loading initial data&#8230; (it may take a while this time)</string>

    <!-- Event Info Contacts -->
    <string name="modify_contacts_txt">Modifica Contatti</string>
    <string name="phone">Telefono</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="website">Sito Web</string>
    <string name="facebook">Facebook</string>
    <string name="twitter">Twitter</string>

    <!-- Event Info When and Where -->
    <string name="date_place_name">data e luogo</string>
    <string name="place_name">Luogo</string>
    <string name="street">Via</string>
    <string name="city">Citta</string>
    <string name="address">Indirizzo</string>
    <string name="date">Data</string>
    <string name="date_with_time">%1$s, ore %2$s</string>
    <string name="start_date">Data di inizio</string>
    <string name="end_date">Data di fine</string>
    <string name="start_time">Ora di Inizio</string>
    <string name="end_time">Ora di Fine</string>
    <string name="duration">Durata</string>

    <!-- Event Info What -->
    <string name="event_desc">Descrizione</string>

    <!-- Event Info Description -->
    <string name="modify_desc_txt">Modifica Descrizione</string>
    <string name="description">Descrivi l\'evento</string>

    <!-- Event Info Tag -->
    <string name="modify_tag_txt">Modifica Tag</string>
    <string name="tag">tag</string>

    <!-- String for the searching fragment -->
    <string name="search_what">Cosa: </string>
    <string name="search_when">Quando: </string>
    <string name="search_where">Dove: </string>
    <string name="search_anytime">Qualsiasi momento</string>
    <string name="search_today">Oggi</string>
    <string name="search_tomorrow">Domani</string>
    <string name="search_thisweek">Questa settimana</string>
    <string name="search_intwoweeks">Nelle prossime due settimane</string>
    <string name="search_inonemonth">Il prossimo mese</string>
    <string name="search_anywhere">Qualsiasi luogo</string>
    <string name="search_within">Entro %s</string>
    <string name="dialog_connection_search">La modalità offline supporta solo la ricerca testuale. Per utilizzare le funzionalità avanzate connettiti ad una rete.</string>
    <string name="search_for">Cerca</string>

    <!-- Menu -->

    <string name="map_view">Vai alla mappa</string>
    <!-- Rating -->
    <string name="ratingtext_average">Giudizio medio:</string>
    <string name="ratingtext_user">Il tuo giudizio: %s</string>
    <string name="ratingtext_raters">Giudizi totali: %s</string>
    <string name="rating_place_dialog_title">Valuta questo luogo:</string>
    <string name="rating_event_dialog_title">Valuta questo evento:</string>
    <string name="comment_event_dialog_title">Commenta questo evento:</string>
    <string name="rating_success">La tua valutazione è stata salvata</string>
    <string name="comment_success">Il tuo commento è stato salvato</string>
    <string name="rate_button">Recensiona!</string>
    <string name="hotel_level">Livello famiglia: %s</string>
    <string name="hotel_cat">Categoria: %s stelle</string>
    <string name="event_subcat">Categoria: %s</string>
    <string name="event_price">Prezzo: %s </string>
    <string name="event_price_free">Prezzo: gratuito</string>
    <string name="audit_person_date">Data conseguimento qualifica: %s</string>
    <string name="auth_required">Si prega di registrarsi con il suo Google account.</string>
    <string name="comment_hint">Commento</string>
    <string name="label_attending">Partecipazione</string>
    <string name="label_comments">Commenti</string>
    <string name="community_attendees">Partecipanti</string>
    <string name="community_attending">Parteciperai all\'evento?</string>
    <string name="vote">Vota anche tu</string>
    <string name="label_rating">Rating</string>
    <string name="community_my_rate">Il mio giudizio</string>
    <string name="community_avg_rate">Giudizio medio</string>
    <string name="community_tot_rate">voti</string>
    <string name="attend_success">Aggiunto alla tua lista di partecipazioni!</string>
    <string name="not_attend_success">Rimosso dalla tua lista di partecipazioni!</string>

    <!-- To know tab -->
    <string name="_toknow_place_type">Tipo di luogo</string>
    <string name="_toknow_access">Accesso</string>
    <string name="_toknow_chance">Probabilità di evento</string>
    <string name="_toknow_language_main">Lingua principale</string>
    <string name="_toknow_clothing">Abbigliamento consigliato</string>
    <string name="_toknow_to_bring">Da portare</string>
    <string name="toknow_button_add">Aggiungi nuove informazioni</string>
    <string name="toknow_label_new">Nuovo \"da sapere\"</string>
    <string name="toknow_label_edit">Modifica \"da sapere\"</string>
    <string name="toknow_label_title">Titolo</string>
    <string name="toknow_label_content">Contenuto</string>
    <string name="toknow_toast_title_empty">Il titolo è vuoto</string>
    <string name="address_select_toast">Selezionare un indirizzo</string>
    <string name="toast_time_wrong">Il tempo dell\'evento è errato</string>
    <string name="when_where">Dove e quando</string>
   
        <!-- create and update -->
<string name="update_success">Le tue modifiche sono state salvate con successo.</string>
 <string name="update_failed">Ci sono stati problemi nel salvataggio delle modifiche. Riprova. </string>
  <string name="terms_of_service">
<![CDATA[
       <b>Introduction<br>
        Applicable worldwide except where we publish specific territorial terms and conditions.</b><br>
These terms and conditions ("Terms") set important information regarding the rights, obligations and restrictions that may apply you as user ("User") when you access to the Internet site at  <a href="http://www.iescities.eu/server">http://www.iescities.eu/server</a> ("Website") or when you access to, download and use the application IES Cities Player ("Application") or whatever the services provided by using it. The application act as a marketplace for those applications developed within the IES Cities framework, allowing users to discover which applications are available on their surroundings making use of public data. Moreover the Application and the Website allow the access to other Applications and Websites. The Website and the Application, where no specifically provided, are supplied by all the partners that make up IES Cities Consortium. IES Cities Project ( <a href="http://www.iescities.eu">http://www.iescities.eu</a>) has received funding from the European Union’s Competitiveness and Innovation Framework Programme under grant agreement nº 325097.
These Terms and conditions are available in the Application installed in your device or in the Website.
The definitive version of this text is the Spanish version any translation of these Terms are provided as a courtesy to you.
You must accept the Terms and other applicable laws regarding the use of IES Cities in case you want to use of the Application, the Website and IES Cities Platform ("Services") 
If you do not agree with these Terms or consider that possible future changes of them will make unacceptable for you, please do not use IES Cities. By using IES Cities including, but not limiting to, the Website, the Application, the Services, updates, etc. we will consider that you accept these Terms and any change we make to them. You accept to use IES Cities only for purposes that are legal, proper and in accordance with these Terms and with any applicable regulation.
We consider you accept the Terms, when you expressly accept them in the installation process of the Application, when you download or update it o when you use it with your device.
<br><br><b>Policy of Use</b><br>
IES Cities is a free application which allows using it with no limitations. You commit to make a reasonable use of the Application and services. Flood or affect the system performance by reading or writing data in excess that affects to the use of the Service by other users, it is a violation of the Terms.
The Application allows you to publish some information. You will be responsible for the information, opinion, comments, etc. you express in IES Cities, directly or by using the Application and/or services. The user commits not to publish, or encourage the publication of:<br> 
a) information that is offensive, discriminatory, humiliating, obscene, etc. or which may cause offence to others in terms of race, religion, sex or ethnicity;<br> 
b) any material which incites the commission of crime; <br>
c) any material is not yours, you don’t have authorization to publish it or infringes copyrights, patents or marks;<br> 
d) advertising, spam, pyramid scheme; <br>
e) information to deceive other users; <br>
f) information on how to exploit security breaches; <br>
g) files containing virus, Trojans or another type of malicious code which can affect to the performance of the Service or to other Users;<br> 
h) files, links or other material which tries to stole other users accounts; <br>
i) any piece of software to collect information from other user; <br>
j) any other thing that circumvents or doesn’t comply with current local laws.<br>
Sometimes you will need to register at the Website and/or some of the applications in order to be able to use them. The User commits to provide real information during the registration process and whenever the Service asks for it. You must update the information when there are any changes in it. In case of suspicion about the veracity of your data we are entitled to suspend your account.
The infringement of the policy of us	<string name="no_empty_comment">Empty comment</string>
e will cause the cancelation of the user account and the rejection to the creation of a new one and we could also apply some methods to avoid the future use of the Application by the banned user.
We can change the Service at any time, adding, modifying or suppressing some of them. We’ll try to communicate those changes in a reasonable way. If you continue using the Service, we understand then you have accepted the changes and the Terms.
<br><br><b> Pay for the Service</b><br>
The Application and the Service provided by IES Cities are cost free.
In case we decide to change the Service or part of it into a pay per use Service we would communicate it and the prices in a reasonable way and enough time to allow the users stop using the Service if they do not want to pay.
The Application may need access to a network for a correct operation. The access to a network may mean additional costs for the use of data networks. These costs aren’t attributable to IES Cities and the User must deal on them.
<br><br><b> Data Privacy</b><br>
When you fill out the registration form in the Website or in some of the applications, you provide some personal data you expect we manage them diligently. Fondazione Buno Kessler ("FBK") and the rest of the partners of the IES Cities consortium will manage data in a suitable way and always in accordance with local regulations or, when applicable, European regulations regarding data protection.
Additionally the User must protect provided account using security means supplied for it, including but no limiting to:  Build a strong password; Change the password frequently; Not to share login data; etc.
FBK and the partners from IES Cities consortium will use data, provided by Users, to manage the use of Website and Application. We do not trade with the data of the users.
FBK and the partners from IES Cities consortium will not collect personal data from users during the use of the Service. They can collect some anonymous statistical data regarding the use of the Service in order to improve the Service or evaluate the use of the different Services
Users can customize the use of the Application and searches determining some filters (they may involve personal data). The filters are stored in the device and never are sent through the network. They are not also collected for any reason.
<br><br><b>  Property of Data</b><br>
The data provided by the Service and accessible through the Website and the Application come from publicly accessible sources or their proprietors allow the use of the by the public, and therefore they maintain the ownership of data.
The collection of data and/or creation of databases from them is not allowed, they are for consult only.
User may access data with no cost. Any derivative works that access these data should allow the access to them with no cost.
Sometimes Users will be able to update, modify, and insert new data into the platform through the Website or the Application. These new data will become part of the public domain as it is the data they are working with. If you intend to publish data in other sites as social networks or third parties websites, please refer to their own privacy policy before publishing anything. We do not pay any reward for the data published by users. We inform you that FBK and the partners from IES Cities consortium may revise all data published by users and remove them when they consider that data are wrong or they violate site goals.
If you intend to retain some rights on your data or obtain any reward for them, please don’t publish in our site.
<br><br><b>  Data Accuracy</b><br>
Data is provided "as is" provided by the data sources. FBK and partners from IES Cities consortium are not responsible for the accuracy of the data or any damage and direct or indirect costs, caused by the use of this information.
<br><br><b> Third Parties</b><br>
Sometimes the user can access some other sites and social networks, external to FBK and partners from IES Cities Consortium and managed by third parties, from the Website or from some of the Application. FBK and partners from IES Cities consortium are not responsible for the privacy policy of those sites.
If you use your social network account to access our Website or to use the Application, FBK and partners from IES Cities consortium will not collect any other information than needed to manage the account and the access to it.
If you publish any information on social networks, through the Application or Website, please note that the data will be subject to the privacy policy and to the terms and conditions of that social network.
<br><br><b> Property of the Application</b> <br>
The Application is property of its authors. The authors grant a non-exclusive and revocable license to copy, install and use the Application in the user devices and to use the Service at no cost. This license does not give to the User any right on the Application property which it will remain on the authors.
<br><br><b>  Availability</b><br>
FBK and partners from IES Cities consortium do not acquire any commitment on the availability of the Website or the information. In any case they will put all their effort to avoid or minimize any interruption of the Service, trying to maximize uptime. Service provider will inform of any scheduled service interruption in a suitable way and it will try to minimize downtime.
FBK and partners form IES Cities consortium aren’t responsible for the damage and direct or indirect costs caused for the service unavailability.<br>
<br><br><b> Legal Protection</b> <br>
We grant to the user a non-exclusive and revocable license to install, copy and use the Application in your devices and to use the Service at no cost.
You agree that you will not use the application to: <br>
a) interfere or manipulate the Service; <br>
b) modify data maliciously; <br>
c) collect data of the users of the application; <br>
d) threaten, disturb, extort to other users; <br>
e) Interfere third parties services; <br>
f) affect third parties copyrights.<br>
The Application is provided "as is" and you use it under your own responsibility. FBK and partners from IES Cities consortium disclaims liability for errors, malfunctions in your terminal, interruptions to other applications, data loss and unavailability, if you use the Application.]]>
    </string>
    <string name="exit_quiz">Grazie per il tuo contributo</string>
    <string name="not_now">Non adesso</string>
    <string name="open_answer">Altro (specificare)</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_welcome_back">Bentornato, vuoi ripartire con il questionario?</string>
    <string name="questionnary_intro">
<![CDATA[
<html>
 <head></head>
 <body style="text-align:justify;color:black;background-color:white;">
Quest\'applicazione e\' parte del progetto europeo IES Cities. Possiamo farti qualche domanda sull\'applicazione? Le sue risposte verranno memorizzate in modo anonimo. Lei puo\' farlo tramite Google Play o direttamente dall\'interno dell\'applicazione </body>
</html>
]]>
    </string>
    <string name="questionnaire_exit">Grazie per il tuo contributo</string>
    <string name="next_quiz">Avanti</string>
    <string name="skip_quiz">Salta</string>
    <string name="categories_event_all">Tutti gli eventi</string>
    <string name="no_empty_comment">Commento vuoto</string>
    <string name="warning_fill_fields">Riempi i campi extra</string>
    <string name="hint_dasapere_content">Inserisci qui il testo</string>
    <string name="hint_dasapere_name">Aggiungi una nuova informazione</string>
    <string name="empty_to_know">Riempi il valore</string>
    <string name="empty_da_sapere">Nessuna informazione aggiuntiva</string>
    <string name="empty_add_informations">
<![CDATA[
         <p>Tocca <img src = \'empty_info\' /> per aggiungere delle informazioni sull\'evento.</p>
    ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="empty_my_events_1">Non hai ancora deciso di partecipare ad un evento!</string>
    <string name="empty_my_events_2">Entra nei dettagli di un evento, dì che parteciparai e l\'evento apparirà in questa lista</string>
    <string name="no_point_to_show_on_map">Nessun event geolocalizzato presente</string>
    <string name="credits">Credits</string>
    <string name="credits_appname">Rovereto Explorer</string>
    <string name="credits_subtitle">Stai cercando qualcosa di interessante da fare a Rovereto?</string>
    <string name="project_by">Un progetto di:</string>
    <string name="collaboration_with">In collaborazione con:</string>
    <string name="credits_info">Per informazioni, segnalazioni o suggerimenti:</string>
    <string name="credits_details">Ulteriori dettagli:</string>
    <string name="update_list">Aggiornando la lista</string>
    <string name="home_banner">Scopri cosa fare a Rovereto</string>
    <string name="questionnaire_error">Errore nell\'inviare i dati</string>
    
    <!-- tabs' strings -->
    <string name="tab_info">Info</string>
    <string name="tab_daSapere">da sapere</string>
    <string name="tab_comunita">Comunità</string>

</resources>